=Love Actually S5 Extra Episode=
(After confession)
Get in the car.
Be careful.
Is it okay?
Yes, no problem.
It's really beautiful.
Okay.
Later, we'll just do it like this.
We'll go in holding the flowers.
Okay.
We'll stun everyone.
This looks good.
You have great taste.
(The look of being praised
by his girlfriend)
The day I held your hand,
I was comparing your finger to mine.
I thought, okay.
It might not be a perfect match,
but as long as it fits
on my pinky, it's fine.
So I bought it for you to wear.
I like this one.
When I made it,
I was quite surprised too.
I said this was made quite nicely.
It is very nice.
How did you make it?
First, paint a black base.
It's like painting an oil painting.
You need to paint a black base first.
Then paint the quartz sand.
After painting the stones on,
then paint the coast.
After the coast, you need
to spread the fluorescent powder
and loose powder.
The key is these waves.
How did you paint them?
I blew them out.
I did it like this.
I can't blow anymore.
(Out of breath)
I'm already dizzy.
We can add each other on WeChat now.
I'll scan your QR code.
(Added personal WeChat)
I'll set an alias and send it to you.
If you send these,
I'll send mine over.
You're definitely going
to send a contact card.
(Wang Yi and Lu Bingkun's chat)
Do I need to send my company brochure?
What are you doing?
So smooth.
Xihui.
What are you doing?
I'm taking purikura photos.
Do you want to take some together?
Come on.
Okay.
Ling, you're so handsome today.
Thanks.
Xihui is taking photos inside.
Xihui.
Hello.
Ling.
Help me take a photo with Hui.
Okay.
Let's find a nice background.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go to the living room.
Sure.
It's the last day today.
The last day.
Let's do it here.
Sit on the sofa.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Good.
This side looks much better.
I'll send these to you later,
and you can pick.
Okay.
Hello.
I bought a lot of food.
Okay.
I ordered a bunch of dishes.
We'll come over in a bit.
We're back.
Where is everyone?
Where is everybody?
Yeah.
- Hello.
You just got back.
Why is there something in Wentao's hair?
What is that?
Glitter.
Bling-bling.
I went clubbing.
(One says anything)
Okay.
(The other believes anything)
I don't have any in my hair.
Yeah, why is that?
You do.
Don't move.
I can't find it.
(Singing)
♪Take the dream away♪
(Harmonizing)
♪Away♪
(Singing again)
♪Raindrops♪
(Busy)
Wait a moment.
I'm not done yet.
Still there?
Dong.
It's great.
It's not coming off.
You're handsome.
Too handsome.
You're handsome too.
It's the most popular style now.
Double-breasted.
You're handsome too.
Come down and eat.
I ordered a lot of dishes.
Okay, let's put our stuff down.
Okay.
Should I eat in my evening gown?
Just wear it.
Really?
Let them see.
Are you serious?
Hi.
Xuan, you look so beautiful.
Let's take photos.
I want to take photos.
Take photos.
Let's go take photos first.
Did things go smoothly for you today?
Yes.
Did you give the letter?
Yes, I did.
How could I not?
What should I do?
That's great.
Come on.
Hurry up.
I've got everything ready.
Just waiting for you guys to come.
Let's first...
take a photo first.
Can we take a group photo?
Xuan.
Let me take a photo with you first.
I just took one with Hui.
Okay.
Good.
Beautiful.
Wait, let's take another one.
Really good.
Very good.
Are you on the phone?
Yes, it's great.
Yeah.
Hold it.
Very good.
Okay, let's change poses.
Professional photographer.
Now giving technical guidance.
Yes, very good.
Keep smiling.
Excellent.
Let's take another one.
(Immersive photo shoot)
Excellent, let's take another one.
Yes.
Very natural.
Very good.
Okay, let's change the angle.
I can't take it anymore.
Let me take one of you two together.
So handsome.
A family of three.
Three.
- Good.
Very good.
Good.
Amazing.
Let's go eat.
How did you spend
your evening, Mr. Dong?
I just bought these dishes for everyone
and then came back.
This food is amazing.
I thought everyone
would be hungry
after coming back from the confession.
Mr. Dong, you're always so thoughtful.
What?
I said, today, I told
Xiao Wentao that I like him.
I can't eat anymore.
No.
There's still plenty of time.
At that point, I wasn't even
thinking about him anymore.
I just focused on my own happiness.
As long as you're happy.
Your outfit.
Have fun.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
(A happy face)
Look.
Isn't this reaction infuriating?
It's so funny.
How do we carry all this stuff?
I want to hold these flowers.
You probably can't carry them.
They're very heavy.
It doesn't matter.
Am I strong?
My mouth is full of glitter.
Why is my mouth
the only one with glitter in it?
Can I add you on WeChat?
I think this looks quite unique.
It is quite pretty.
Come.
Let me carry it.
You do it.
Take a photo of us two.
Let's go.
Beautiful.
What is wrong with you?
What is this little show?
Beautiful, can I add you on WeChat?
You scan my QR code.
Scan mine.
Honolulu.
Right.
What does it mean?
Honolulu.
Lulu.
What does it mean?
It's the one I like.
Honolulu in Hawaii.
You should show the camera
the first thing you sent.
Say it. Who starts a chat...?
Say it.
Who starts a chat by calling someone
girlfriend right after adding them?
(Xu Lvyang and Zhou Youling's chat)
Then what should you reply?
Okay, let me reply.
Big Bro, this vibe.
Big Bro, you're amazing.
How many flowers are these?
Can I even count them?
999.
Solid.
Come on.
Eat.
Eat something.
I got a bunch of stuff
that I know you two love.
It's all Sichuan cuisine.
Really?
Come.
Waiting for you to take the group photo.
A group photo for the girls.
Your hair.
It's fine.
Don't pick it up for him.
That's a sign of his success.
Alright, fine.
(Symbol of success)
(I have one too)
You're so handsome.
There's something in your hair.
I still have a leaf in my hair?
Do I have anything in my hair?
No, you don't.
You're clean.
Clean.
Hi.
It really looks like a wedding.
- Get married.
It really looks like you just
came back from your wedding.
You two should come over to toast.
Come on.
Toast everyone.
Is this the outfit you two specifically
changed into for toasting
after the confession?
Yes.
Mine is the wine-pouring outfit.
Come on over.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Let me introduce her.
This is my girlfriend.
Well,
does anyone else want to do this?
Let me do this too.
This is my girlfriend.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You all look so handsome
and so beautiful today.
Xuan, you look so beautiful.
You're blocking it.
Your dress is very beautiful too.
Blessings.
I have something in my room.
Can you help me get it?
My thing.
Next to Ruita's blanket.
There's a plastic bag, a white one.
It's for everyone.
It's inconvenient for me right now.
Thank you, my boyfriend.
(Out-of-nowhere PDA)
What mysterious thing?
I wrote a card
for each person.
We are...
Waiting eagerly.
We're all ears.
Come on.
I'm dressed so formally today.
To Xihui.
You, who are bright,
cheerful, and empathetic,
have always been taking care of
everyone's emotions.
Though you seem carefree,
you're actually gentle and delicate.
I hope you, with your amazing hair,
have fewer worries.
Don't always think
too much about others.
Sometimes, be a little selfish.
Often,
I can't help but stare at you
because you are
too beautiful and wonderful.
Your eyes are always
bright and innocent.
Sometimes, you come out
with a few dad jokes
that make everyone laugh.
Thank you for your "fish not sticking".
"Fish not sticking".
I'm happy
for your mutual love.
From Ruita.
To Mr. Dong.
My best opposite-sex friend
in the Love House.
Also one of the Goofy Earth Sign Trio.
Mr. Dong
is also a humorous and witty man.
A health guru.
I hope you can find
someone who loves you back
and truly gets you
and live the life you like
with just two of you sharing three meals
a day through all four seasons.
Earth signs are slow
to warm up in love, yet steady,
reserved, and sincere.
When the sun comes out,
the stars disappear.
But on the back of the card,
the sun, stars, and moon are all there.
I think you will definitely meet someone
who understands all your stars
and can watch the sunrise
and sunset with you.
You definitely will.
You can do it, bro.
The sun and moon shining together.
This is so you.
Thank you.
Bingkun.
I want to borrow
your girlfriend for a hug.
Do it.
Bro.
Call him bro.
To Zhou Youling.
(Suddenly called on)
The back is my photography skill level.
I didn't expect Xuehua Bing
and I would become roasting friends.
You're sunny, dashing,
1.9 meters tall, rich, handsome,
and perfect.
Thanks for enduring an "anti-fan's"
(Taking ugly photos of Zhou Youling)
attacks for a month.
Happy for you.
May your career, business,
and love all go smoothly.
PS:
Be well with Liu.
From Ruita.
Thank you.
What do you say?
To thank this "anti-fan"?
I need to send you to a training class.
(Photography class spot reserved)
You'll pay the tuition, right?
Sure.
To Liu.
Your gentle beauty is like a flower.
Every time I see you,
I can't help but look a few more times.
I have a feeling
of wanting to protect you.
I hope you and Youling will be well.
Be brave to be yourself.
Shine and be beautiful.
PS:
Don't turn off the power
of the moon in the sky.
To Danqi.
Every time I see you,
I feel your gentleness.
I appreciate
your independence and talent
and your sincerity and bravery.
In my heart,
you are the template
for a semi-mature woman
who's graceful, decent,
gentle, and firm.
You, who are sensitive,
always empathize
with everyone's emotions.
You thoughtfully prepare
daily necessities for everyone.
And you draw for everyone.
As we talk,
you're always the first to shed tears.
I love you and appreciate you
more than you imagine.
You will definitely find
a beautiful love.
The one that suits you
might be coming soon.
May your career and brand
sell like crazy.
Let me give you one too.
I want one too.
Love you.
Don't cry. You're crying again.
Don't cry.
To Xuan.
This is you in my eyes.
The domineering queen "slays" me.
I'm screaming.
Every time I see you,
your smiling eyes shine with light.
In my eyes,
you are a gentle little woman.
Parentheses:
But your figure is striking.
Even with sound effects. You...
You like to do everything by yourself.
You were hurt,
but you worried about us instead.
So from now on, leave those things
to your man.
Haha.
Wishing your career goes smoothly.
We could grab a drink
and knit together sometime.
Silently loving you.
From Ruita.
I love you.
- Thank you.
- Give me a kiss.
To Wentao.
This suits Wentao so well.
It was also drawn here.
You love freedom and space.
You have the wake-up tune
and the love for music.
May you shine in the field you love,
great chef of the house.
Parentheses: You do perfect fried eggs.
Let's meet up often.
Come to Shanghai often to see Xuan.
Thank you.
I started it off well.
Lu Bingkun is like,
"It made me feel so bad."
I'm fine.
To Lizheng.
A fish.
Isn't it the most handsome fish?
Congratulations
for sticking to the brightest,
most compatible Hui fish
in the semi-mature pond.
May you, who are brave, pure,
excellent, and sunny,
be rich forever.
This blessing is great.
We agreed to go together
to Xiamen in the next few days.
From Ruita, the "daughter" of Hui,
whom you love.
It's full of details.
Let's do a divination.
(Sorry)
Well...
It's fine.
Bingkun is like, "Forget it."
I'll first...
To BK.
Look at the words on the back
and look at me across from you.
The words on the back are:
You are a very loving person.
And your life
will be filled with romance,
with Ruita.
And there's another one
that I happened to find here.
I love you just the way you are.
The one for BK is a bit special.
We've seen it before,
but...
Let's toast everyone.
We can loosen up a bit today.
That's great.
Cheers!
You two have to get married.
There's no other way.
Really.
Today it already looks like you're in
a wedding dress, and...
We're having a toasting part.
So happy.
Cheers.
Let's do the arm-in-arm toast.
Take a photo.
Send it to the group.
Finish it.
A small arm-in-arm toast.
Let's take
a big group photo.
Come on, let's take a big group photo.
Come on.
Semi-mature family,
together forever!
(Observation room's recording day)
Let's give another round of applause
to Love Actually S5's
all couple guests.
The next game is called
Love Me, Praise Me.
There are two rounds in total.
In the first round, the four guys
take turns complimenting the girls.
In the second round, the girls line up
and take turns complimenting the guys.
No repeating.
Until
you're out when you're silent
for three seconds.
We'll go until the end to see who wins.
Let's have the guys go first, okay?
Do you want to talk some smack?
I can't see how I'd lose.
Mr. Zhou.
He can't see how he'd lose.
Then you should just lose.
Ling Lizheng,
hurry.
I'll quote from Xihui.
Stay steady. We can win.
Xiaowen.
You probably won't be able
to leave this studio today.
We'll be recording until midnight.
Wait a moment.
I want to leave this studio.
Can you chat among yourselves?
I have a family and kids.
Get ready.
Okay.
Come on.
Ready? Go.
(Love Me, Praise Me)
(Round 1)
Very pretty.
Cute.
Nice voice.
Sunny.
Adorably clueless.
Lively.
Good videos.
Cheerful.
Optimistic.
Quirky.
Can play tennis.
Humorous.
(Already dizzy)
Loves to act cute.
Good fashion sense.
Cute.
"Cute" was already said.
Already said.
Xihui.
Too competitive.
(Ling Lizheng out)
Come on.
Three, two, one, continue.
Good taste.
Praising yourself?
Succubus.
What?
Even a succubus came out.
You really are...
Cooks well.
Good at styling.
Ladylike.
Her hair color is nice.
Excellent cooking taste.
Too much?
Taste?
That was repeated, right?
What's that?
Excellent taste.
Too much excellent taste.
He said "cooking".
Cooking.
Good figure.
Her dress is nice.
Very caring.
It's nonstop.
Sweet.
She has a great figure.
Great figure.
"Great figure" was already said.
I let you have your way.
Thank you, Wentao.
Thank you.
We can get off work tonight.
Thank you, Wentao.
I was so scared.
Match point.
BK
and Zhou Youling, go.
Three, two, one, go.
(Love Me, Praise Me)
(First round match point)
Very self-consistent.
Self-consistent.
Strong work ability.
Already said.
Was it said?
It was said.
(Lu Bingkun wins)
Congratulations, BK.
I really couldn't see how to lose.
Actually, I think in the end,
it's just a memory contest.
Yeah.
(Love Me, Praise Me)
(Round 2)
Do you want to talk some smack?
Of course.
Then I definitely won't lose.
Because Zhou Youling's strengths
are more than the stars.
In my eyes, BK's strengths
double the stars.
Come on, a galaxy.
Come on.
What did you just say?
You said you couldn't see
how you'd lose.
I'll show you.
No.
Wait.
She should talk smack at the girls.
Not the guys.
Why are you getting worked up with me?
The girls are all too nice.
I can't bring myself to be mean.
Because he beat her boyfriend.
She wants to get back at him.
Understood.
(Every debt has its debtor)
Then I can only say,
ladies,
go for it.
Come on.
In the order we just had,
line up.
Okay, come on.
Three, two, one, go.
Tallest height.
(Smiling lightly)
Independent.
Good figure.
That's true.
Handsome.
Ambitious.
Mature.
Sincere.
Can play the trumpet.
Thoughtful.
Won't make you worry.
Straightforward.
Good fashion sense.
Filial.
Emotional value.
The girls have so many words.
Well,
they have a much richer vocabulary
than us guys.
You know?
Has a contrast.
Has a good mole.
Has a good mole?
Strong.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Okay, next, let's start from Ruita.
Come on.
Three, two, one, go.
Can catch the joke.
Catch the joke.
Handsome without makeup.
Good singer.
Filial.
"Filial" has been said.
Okay, get ready.
Match point.
Three, two, one, go.
His slicked-back hair looks cute.
Caring.
"Caring" has been said.
Then let's congratulate Hui
for winning.
Now do you know how you lost?
Hui used his cute side profile,
cute front face, cute slicked-back hair,
and cute bangs
to beat everyone.
If one person in a pair wins,
that pair won't be punished.
So Zhou and Liu,
and Xuan and Xiaowen,
you guys have to receive a punishment.
Okay.
The punishment for the two couples
is five princess-carry squats.
That's too easy.
I often carry my husband.
Come on.
Evonne.
Show everyone.
It's the girl carrying.
Evonne.
Respect.
You're quite tall and heavy.
You have some weight.
I'm quite heavy.
Princess carry.
Squat.
One.
Two.
Three.
Very easy.
Four.
Five.
Very easy.
Xiaowen and Xuan.
She'll carry me five times.
I'm not doing five times with you.
You let Xuan carry you?
So easy.
You just want to be dominated.
You're really strong.
Alright.
Let's give another round of applause
to the four couples.
Thank you.
We shipped it.
See you next season.
The production team.
What is with this voiceover of yours?
Xuan's emotional value is maxed out.
Bossy CEO.
Like you just got off work.
You just got off work.
You're married.
Let's do a live version now.